[indistinct chattering]
You clean up very nicely,
if you don't mind me saying so.
I don't mind you saying so.
Thanks.
You look pretty much the same
as you always look.
- Oh. Really?
- Yes.
- This is my date outfit.
- Really?
Is this your first date? I mean,
um, since your wife died?
Do I seem out of practice?
- Hi.
Uh, my name's Gerard. I'll be
your server this evening.
Would you like
to hear our specials?
I'm sorry
to interrupt, Gerard
but I'm getting a message
from, uh, your mother.
- A Janet no, um, Janis.
- Yes.
Um..
'I'm sorry for your loss.'
She's happy now.
And she wants you to know that
she sends her deepest love.
And, um..
...your uncle, Ed says,
"roll tide."
Does that mean anything
to you, "roll tide"?
[Gerard]
'My mother's brother Edward.
He died five years ago.'
He was a tight end
at Alabama in the '60s.
Oh.
Uh, they're called
the Crimson Tide.
Uh, that's their rallying cry,
"roll tide."
Oh.
Well, uh, I'd like to have
the soup du jour
and the lamb, medium
and the arugula salad
and the fish for the lady.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Thanks.
[clears throat]
- What?
- Oh, come on.
You're so ferocious
in your lack of faith.
I mean, is it so hard to imagine
that I'm not putting on an act?
That, that I really am
what I say I am?
His mother sent a message.
I'm meant to help. That's all.
It happens to me
all the time.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Roll tide.
[alert chimes]
[telephone ringing]
[sighs]
Bad guys just
keep on coming, huh?
I hate the internet.
Listen, if you like,
I can deal. You go.
No, it's okay.
It's just a web alert
for when a name
we're interested in pops up.
[clicking mouse]
Wayne?
What is it?
Oh.
This is not good.
Relax, it's,
it's just a hoax.
It's staged,
almost certainly.
[intense music]
[Van Pelt]
'Oh, my God!'
[gasps]
- I didn't put-- uh, no.
- Yes.
[laughing]
No. no.
- You went to jail, really?
- Yes, I did.
- What's so hard to believe?
- For how long?
I was there for two days
and two very luxurious nights.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
And how'd you get out?
- I just escaped.
- Uh-huh.
I don't believe you
for one second.
It wasn't, it wasn't that
difficult. It's all timing.
Uh-huh.
- I'm not kidding. Okay.
- Uh-huh.
Excuse me.
I have to go to the bathroom.
[laughing]
Ah, thank you.
[sighs]
[instrumental music]
[indistinct chattering]
[sighs]
Hey.
'Kristina, um..'
[cellphone rings]
Oh. I'm so sorry.
[beep]
It's work. Hello.
Jane, you need to come
to the office right now.
[intense music]
[theme music]
[instrumental music]
[gasps and whimpers]
[screaming]
[video fast-forwarding]
[music continues]
it was posted on the internet
an hour ago
on a popular notice board.
There's a message
that goes with it.
"I am becoming
what I was meant to be.
'Your children's children
will worship me."'
We don't know when or where
the video was made.
There appears to be
an '08 Silverado
parked outside the house
so it's gotta be
at least that recent.
Has Red John made videos
or issued statements
like this before?
- No.
- Oh, thank you.
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt.
Oh. Hi, Kristina.
Uh, good to see you.
Yeah. That poor girl.
Yeah, yeah.
For what it's worth
I'm getting a sense
that she died very recently.
Her body will be discovered
very soon. She's near water.
Does this feel like
Red John to you?
Uh, I'm not getting
a read on that.
The whole internet aspect is
interesting, though, isn't it?
I mean,
why put it up there?
This clip's had over a million
viewers. A desire for fame?
[Hightower]
'Patrick, you're
being very quiet.'
What are you thinking?
Uh, I'd have to see
the crime scene.
CHP just reported
a homicide in the Bay Area.
'Smiley face on the wall.'
'College student
named Marley Sparrow.'
'Roommate found her, called it
in about a half-hour ago.'
Let's get ready to go.
- Bay area?
- Uh, yes.
That is close to water.
That's, uh, that's uncanny.
Oh, come on.
That's pretty good.
I am feeling a strong connection
to this case somehow.
Madeline,
can we have a word, please?
Yeah.
[Hightower]
'Excuse us.'
She's gonna ask
if she can come along with us.
Now obviously, that's your call.
But I hope that you refuse
because I won't work with her.
I will quit.
What's your objection?
If she can help us, why not?
Nothing she says
is more than clever guesswork.
So she has essentially
the same skills as you.
Without all the drama.
What's the deal?
Red John is mine.
Okay. Okay, I hear you.
[whispers]
Thank you.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
- Oh, please.
- Uh..
Um, I was going to offer
my services
but I get the sense
Mr. Jane is telling you
that he won't work with me.
The last thing I want to do
is upset this investigation
but if I have any more
feelings about the case
could I call you?
Of course, Kristina.
Always be glad
to hear your thoughts.
- Have a goodnight.
- Thank you.
[whispers]
Okay.
- Listen, uh, I--
- I completely understand.
- No hard feelings.
- Okay.
That was an unusual date,
though, huh?
- Yes, very.
- Thank you.
I'll see you soon,
I hope.
[elevator bell rings]
[elevator doors open]
- Um, would you--
- Oh, yeah, sure.
Oh.
- Bye.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[camera shutter clicking]
Guys, give me
a minute, please.
Thank you.
[instrumental music]
[whispers]
Hey, Marley. We'll get
this sorted out for you.
[music continues]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Hey, hey,
Patrick Jane.
Long time.
'So, que pasa,dude?'
My people need
to do their thing.
I won't be long.
Oh.
[clears throat]
'You hoovering up the, uh,
ol' psychic ectoplasm?'
[makes buzzing sounds]
Yeah, that's exactly
what I'm doing.
We have a schedule to keep,
amigo.Tick-tock.
Sooner you're done
fooling around
sooner my people can find
actual clues.
She's from Iowa.
She played the guitar.
She liked dark chocolate
sudoku and snowboarding.
Shy, but strong.
Honorable, modest.
Didn't drink or smoke.
Parents died
when she was very young.
And after college,
she wanted to go into family law
and help foster kids
like herself.
Or become a singer.
She hadn't made up her mind yet.
Yeah, that's great, dude.
But where's Red John?
Oh, this wasn't Red John.
So you say.
So I say.
[whispers]
Jerk.
Oh, make sure
you have your people
send those papers and journals
to the CBI office.
- Will do.
- Thank you.
[indistinct chattering]
[sniffles]
[female #1]
'Marley was the best.'
'The best person.'
A beautiful soul.
[Lisbon]
'Ruth, you found her body, yes?'
When you entered your house,
did you notice
anything unusual
before you found the body?
Something missing
or out of place?
No, I don't think so.
- How long had you been gone?
- Two days, snowboarding.
Marley was supposed to come
but then her boyfriend
was coming over to see her,
so she stayed.
- Boyfriend's name?
- Grady Shipp.
He's a policeman
in San Francisco.
They've been dating
for, like, a month.
Okay. What was he like?
Nice guy?
Marley really liked him
a lot.
Said he was super nice.
But I don't know.
We never actually met him.
No?
She'd go to his place,
mostly.
And when he came by here,
he'd wait for her in his car.
Weird, no?
I think Marley was
a bit embarrassed
for hooking up with a cop,
you know?
So she kept him
on the down low.
Embarrassed, why?
Marley was cool.
And, well, cops are sort of
nerds with guns, aren't they?
Ruth, hello?
No offense.
[laughing]
Sorry.
'Marley sparrow?'
Yes, I was her academic advisor
for two semesters.
Nice enough girl,
but not as clever
as she likes to think she is.
But none of 'em are,
are they? Ha!
Did you notice any changes
in her behavior recently?
No. But nor do I
pay close attention.
They're all empty vessels
to be filled with knowledge.
Here is
a horrible coincidence.
Last semester, I taught
a criminology elective.
Murder, myth and marketing,
the serial killer as commodity.
Red John
was actually mentioned
in our class discussions.
Isn't that eerie?
Who mentioned him?
What'd they say?
Oh, damned if I know.
It was eight or nine months ago.
Do you have a student list
from the class?
You know, I do.
I do. Somewhere.
[lowered voice]
I do.
We would love
to get a look at that list.
[indistinct chattering]
Thanks.
So there's no Grady Shipp
with any San Fran Police Agency.
There's no
Grady Shipp, period.
There was
a Grady Shipp once.
He killed and ate
his next-door neighbors
in little rock back in the '90s.
He was lethally injected
by the state of Arkansas
in '02.
Huh. So Marley's boyfriend
doesn't want anybody
to see his face, and he named
himself after a cannibal.
'That's two strikes
against him.'
Shame we don't have
a name or a description.
The roommate, Ruth, said that
he never got out of his car.
Maybe we can get
a make and model from her.
Grady Shipp.
In 1989, he did a 6-month spell
in the same wing
at Lompoc as Orval Tanner.
- Orval Tanner?
- Red John's friend.
You have the entire Lompoc
Prison registry in your head?
Well, only
the relevant sections.
[Lisbon]
'Wh-what does it mean?
Is it a joke?'
[Rigsby]
'Marley's boyfriend
is Red John.'
[Cho]
'That doesn't make
any sense.'
In the hunt for this beast
known as "Red John."
well, he--
he's not a beast, Jackie.
He's a human being.
Now he has done
terrible things
but he is still
capable of redemption..
...like all of us.
Red John..
...if you're listening
to us now
I urge you to reach out
and get help.
You can change.
[indistinct chattering]
[instrumental music]
What the hell
are you thinking?
Don't you understand
who you're dealing with?
I do understand, yes.
No, you don't. Clearly,
you don't understand.
I asked Miss Frye here
so that I could fully
express my deep dismay.
I was speaking
from the heart.
That may be, but you were also
hustling for business.
'And that's okay, but you
present me now with a problem.'
We don't have any obligation
to protect you, but--
I wasn't asking for protection.
It's completely unnecessary.
Red John
is not coming after me.
Are you blind?
You've done exactly what I did.
I went on television and talked
about him as though I knew him
and he killed
my wife and child.
Patrick, he was punishing you
because you lied about him.
'I was telling the truth.
He won't take offense with me.'
He might even listen
to what I said.
In fact,
I-I believe he will.
People do change, Patrick.
It's possible.
Agent Hightower, I'm truly
sorry for dismaying you.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have some other appointments.
[inhales deeply]
She needs 24-hour protection.
The best that you can provide.
The Sac PD
Special Protection Unit
will provide security,
the CBI will be on the inside
bodyguarding Miss Frye. Jane
and I will take the first shift.
The next 24-hour rotation
will be split among us
alternating with
the Sparrow case.
Well, we're gonna have to stop
protecting her sooner or later.
That's when he'll go for her.
He'll just wait.
Van Pelt,
what do you got?
We're looking
for Grady Shipp, right?
This is
Marley's address book.
That's different writing. Maybe
that's Grady Shipp himself.
- Can I?
- 'Keep digging.'
Rigsby, take Cho with you.
Check it out.
Yeah, you got it.
[clank]
Hello?
[door creaking]
[flapping sounds]
Hello?
[intense music]
[sighs]
[music continues]
- Blood.
- Yep.
[exhales]
Pig's blood, maybe.
For practice?
[footsteps approaching
[gunshots]
[panting]
[intense music]
Police! Stop!
Hey! Stop!
[engine revving]
Damn!
I'll call it in.
[panting]
What is it?
A lens cap.
Interesting.
Practicing
the Red John symbol
and not just watching us
pursue him
but filming the pursuit.
What does it mean?
It means Marley Sparrow's
killer loves cameras.
He's a voyeur, a fanboy,
a slasher movie geek.
Huh.
Great. But where does
that take us now? Like in a car?
Well, try
the campus film club.
Alright.
Nice place, huh?
Tasteful.
To me, it looks like we're
about to pay way too much money
to get our legs waxed.
- Hmm.
- Hi.
I was just making some lunch.
Would you like something to eat?
Sure, thanks.
I'm good.
Thanks.
Patrick, uh,
on reflection
I'm truly sorry
for the situation I put you in.
I hadn't thought through
your involvement.
Alright, alright.
I-I-I'll eat some lunch.
Just please
don't make a fuss.
Miss Ketchum?
[gasps]
Oh, policemen.
Okay. I knew
I'd forgotten something. Uh..
Okay.
There it is.
I thought
for sure I'd sent that.
- Sent what?
- Uh, the class list.
Of the students
in my criminology class.
Your colleague
had asked for it.
And you're chair
of the film club also?
I have that honor.
You know what?
I have the film club register
here as well.
Okay. Yes, yes.
Would you like to see it?
Yes. That would be,
uh, good.
Okay.
Ah, there you go.
And where were you
Tuesday night, Miss Ketchum?
Oh, how thrilling!
- Am I a suspect?
- Are you?
Well..
I'd like to think I can still
summon that kind of passion.
So where were you?
Home. Alone.
Reading a murder mystery,
actually.
Now there's only one name
on both lists. Wesley Blankfein.
Oh, wait.
You just made a face.
Well, he is a sweet boy.
Rather a good actor, actually.
- But, uh, strange.
- Strange? How?
I can't really
put my finger on it.
It's a look in his eyes.
[male #1]
Yep, that's him.
I remember when he moved in.
I mentioned to him
he was a little older
than most of our students
and he said he needed to escape
from his mother.
[laughs]
[clears throat]
Which, uh, I thought
was an odd response.
And when
did you last see him?
- Uh, three weeks ago..
- Excuse me.
Uh, maybe. I figured
he had a girlfriend.
- 'Nothing here.'
- Oh, hey, Dylan.
[Cho]
'Oh, hey, you guys.
Quick question.'
Now you guys said
Marley's boyfriend
waited for her
outside in a car?
Yes.
Do you recall
what type of car he drove?
Um, it was black, I think.
I'm bad with cars.
It was a,
it was a black SUV.
- What car did Blankfein drive?
- Uh, he didn't have a car.
Huh. Okay.
Try locating
Blankfein's mother.
Maybe she knows where he is.
Alright. Let me know.
Wesley Blankfein's
in the wind.
Looks like
he might be good for this.
I don't think so.
Marley made contact with me.
The name "Blankfein"
doesn't resonate.
- Marley made contact with you?
- Yes.
Of course. Uh, I think
we might have had enough of your
crime-fighting skills, Kristina.
Might be best to stick
to the crystal therapy
and the, uh...foot massages?
- Reflexology.
- Right.
[phone ringing]
'Reflexology.'
This is Lisbon.
[Fenton]
'Agent Fenton, FBI.
Yeah, we got a case'
here in Lake Tahoe.
Looks like your boy Red John.
Victim's name is
a Jacqueline Sandoval.
'You wanna come take a look?'
You can smile
your arrogant smile
and act like you know
everything about everything
but you don't.
There are whole worlds that you
can't even begin to understand.
Synchronized swimming
is, uh, the only world
that springs to mind.
But I'm sure you're right.
There may be many others.
What's the matter?
Red John killed the woman
who interviewed you.
Oh, my God.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct radio chatter]
It's Red John, alright.
Okay, uh, I'll reach out
to the feds.
I'll make sure
they keep us in the loop.
We gotta get back
to Kristina Frye's place.
There are cops all around
her house. Van Pelt is with her
and there's other CBI agents
on their way. She's safe.
I am confident
Red John's not gonna go there.
- That is exactly why he might.
- If he does, we'll get him.
You really wanna hang out
at Kristina's house
waiting for Red John
to show up?
Let's just go back
to the office
and we'll work
the Marley Sparrow case.
There's nothing useful
that I can do there.
This Blankfein character,
he looks good for it, right?
Fine. Go and wait for Red John.
It's not a good idea, though.
Hey, we're in Nevada.
You can't just walk off
and leave me here.
- Hey.
- 'Hey, boss.
So Wesley Blankfein's mother
is Myra Hauser-Blankfein.
Address in Franklin Heights.
And she owns a black SUV
like Grady Shipp drives.
Good. Go check her out.
Now? Well, it's
a long drive.
You leave now,
you'll be there by the morning.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[instrumental music]
Grace, thank you.
How you doing?
I'm doing fine.
Red John certainly
made his point.
Quite possibly,
he'll leave things be now.
I know he will.
I have a clear vision of him.
'He needs to create fear,
that's all.'
He's done that now,
and he feels calm.
'And I'm perfectly safe.'
Will you just stop
that nonsense?
You wanted to promote
your psychic business
and, and you made
a big mistake.
Now will you just,
will you please just own it?
Why are you here?
I am here because
I want to protect you.
And how are you
gonna protect me?
If Red John comes through
that door right now
what are you gonna do,
hypnotize him?
I will do what I need to do.
If Red John wants
to reach me, he will.
I choose to believe
that he doesn't want to.
- Now please, go away.
- I'm gone.
[door closes]
Uh, you're wasting your time.
Ma'am, we're looking
for Mrs. Blankfein and her son.
Gone. And left the cats
to starve. It's not right.
Do you know where they went?
Uh, nope.
Never leaves before. Never.
Every day, 11 o'clock,
like a machine
she's watching her TV shows.
Three days now I hear nothing.
Quiet like the grave.
How about her son Wesley?
Have you seen him?
Nope. Gone, too.
Did it occur to you
that Mrs. Blankfein
might be dead in there?
Yes, it did.
But there'd be a smell,
wouldn't there, if she was dead?
Step back inside,
please, ma'am.
- You good?
- Yeah.
[meowing]
[Wayne]
'Bedroom's clear.'
[Kimball]
'Rigsby.'
Oh, jeez.
"G.S" Grady Shipp.
Bingo.
Inside the mind
of Wesley Blankfein..
- AKA Grady Shipp.
- Not pretty.
It looks like he's obsessed
with Marley
so he builds a shrine
and he fakes up all these photos
of them together.
'Then he tries to turn
the fantasy into reality'
'and posing as Grady Shipp,
he asks her out'
'and she says yes. Big mistake.
Fantasy and reality collide'
and she dies.
[Teresa]
'Sounds about right.'
Where the hell is he?
Uh, where's his mom?
You didn't find anything
useful in the apartment?
- No computer, nothing?
- No. A lot of cats.
Now the pictures of Marley,
they were all taken
at different times and places.
The pictures of Wesley
were all taken
in the same place.
'Nowhere we've been.'
Maybe that's
a safe house for him.
Nothing to say
where it is, though.
- Jane, you wanna take a look?
- Huh?
See if you see anything useful?
Yeah, sure.
If you like.
[instrumental music]
Hmm.
- Yep.
- And..
There's a photo of Wesley
with a sign in the distance
a yellow KC
backward on a pole.
His, his shadow
is pointing right to it.
[Wayne]
'Yeah. It's way small
back there, but I see it.'
Yeah, that's the logo
for Kenny's Chili..
Southern California
fast food chain.
There's about 50 or so outlets.
You memorize trademarks?
Well, with Wesley's long shadow
and the golden light
that would say afternoon.
And sun is in the West
so that puts Kenny's
due East of this location
about a block and a half,
I'd say.
Huh. He's right.
50 or so outlets?
Hardware store
and a liquor store
on the block right next to it.
That should narrow it down.
I'll get on it.
- Thank you.
- Oh. No.
You should make that call.
- What call?
- Right.
Like I'm not
a detective, too?
Hey, Jane. It's Grace.
Kristina's taking a nap.
'I can get her for you
if you like.'
I'd appreciate that, Grace.
Thank you.
Kristina?
Kristina,
it's Jane for you.
Open the door.
Kristina? Kristina?
'Kristina?'
'Kristina!'
How did Kristina
get past the guards?
We don't know.
But she also packed a bag
she took her passport
and her credit cards
so we can
assume she wasn't abducted.
No, no, no. You, you,
you can't assume.
Red John could've gotten
in and taken her.
Maybe. But the likelihood is
she panicked
and ran somewhere to hide.
Yeah. Or, or, or maybe
he lured her out somehow.
We'll check
the phone records.
Let's start contacting
her relatives and friends.
She's out there somewhere.
Forgive me, Agent Lisbon,
but belay that order.
The search for Kristina Frye
will now be conducted
by the missing persons unit.
What?
They're the best
at what they do.
They will find her
if she can be found.
And, Van Pelt, snap out of it.
Wasn't your fault.
- Yes, ma'am, but--
- 'Move on.'
Alright. Where are we
on the Marley Sparrow case?
We have a suspect at large
by the name of Wesley Blankfein.
He's been obsessed with both
Red John and Marley Sparrow.
He seems to have created
an alter ego
by the name of Grady Shipp.
'It's after a killer
with Red John connections.'
Any leads?
Well, off photos he took, we've
ID'd six possible locations
for what we assume
is Blankfein's safe house.
It's pretty much a long shot,
but it's all we have.
Okay. Alright. Go to it.
Let's start
divvying up the locations.
Cho, you take riverside county.
Bring Rigsby with you.
Van pelt and I will take
the San Bernardino locations.
Jane, you stay here.
Take a break.
- I don't need a break.
- I think you do.
I-I-I'd rather keep active.
You're too hyped up
to be out in the field.
- Oh, that's nonsense.
- I agree with Lisbon.
Get some rest.
Some rest? Oh, just..
[chuckles]
Lie down and catch up
on some Zs.
Kick back with
a good book. Rest?
- I'm fine.
- Debatable.
Do you want me to ask
the psych counselor
for an evaluation?
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
Sorry.
- 'Tracy, can you mail this?'
- 'Sure. You got it, hon.'
[indistinct chatter]
[Teresa on tape]
'Leave a message.
I'll call you back.'
Lisbon, it's Jane.
Uh, I found it.
It's 52 North Esperanza.
Hotel Del Dorona
in Salinger Mill.
Uh, I am gonna..
Uh, I-I'm gonna wait for you
at, uh, Kenny's okay?
Give me a call
when you get this message.
Thank you.
[instrumental music]
[indistinct chatter]
[music continues]
[grunting]
[sighs]
[groaning]
[rustling]
'Welcome, detective.'
I'm Grady Shipp.
'So good of you
to come visit me.'
You're a lucky man.
Very lucky.
Tonight, you will have
the dying honor..
Can we do that again?
Tonight..
...you will have
the honor of dying
'as a sacrifice'
to the holy master,
Red John.
Behold, the blood sacrament
of the master.
Stop. You wanna try
that again?
Huh?
Just t-try it again.
Uh, say it like you mean it.
You know,
where's the passion gone?
Behold the blood sacrament
of the master.
'Oh, n-n-no. I'm not.. I'm not..
I'm not buying it. Come on.'
Just, just stop for a sec
and think, think about
what you're doing here
and then we'll start again
from the top, okay?
Uh..
It's alright, Wesley.
I know what's going on.
They've got your mother,
don't they?
Yeah. How'd you know?
They're forcing you
to play a part
in their sick little movie.
Yes.
You're playing the part
of Grady Shipp, right?
Yes.
It's okay. It's okay.
Dylan! Ruth!
We need to talk.
Thank you very much
for totally ruining
a freaking brilliant scene,
you jerk.
Hush, Dyl.
How did you know
it was us?
Well, you were the only people
that mentioned Grady Shipp.
He was your creation.
And it was you
that killed Marley
'wasn't it, Dylan?'
Wesley couldn't hurt a fly.
It was a truly sick individual
that did that.
It was me, actually.
Oh.
'Dyl's much better
with the camera'
and Marley,
deserved what she got.
Pious little bitch.
Keep the camera running.
This is all good stuff.
no offense, but you
wouldn't know good stuff
if it smacked you in the face.
This is just
a corny slasher movie.
Yeah, but real, dude.
Real blood. Real guts.
Yours. Wesley, let's, uh,
wrap this scene up now, okay?
Gonna pick it up
right at the end
behold the blood, etcetera
and then stab
this sucker, okay?
[laughing]
- 'I don't know.'
- That's it.
What? Wh-what are you?
Not.. No!
Okay, this, this man is dead.
Okay, the only question is
'whether you and your mom want
to live or you want to die'
'like him, okay?
That's your choice here.'
These people are nuttier
than a fruitcake.
'They're gonna kill
you regardless.'
- 'You don't have to do this.'
- We are not monsters, Wesley.
We're artists!
'We are making art.'
When the movie's done
of course
you and your mom
are free to go
with our gratitude
for your help.
Stay calm.
Behold the blood.
Wesley.
I'm sorry.
Wesley, Wesley, hey.
- Behold..
- No, Wesley.
The blood sacrament..
- No. It's okay.
- 'Of the master!'
Wesley!
[gunshot]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[panting]
No. No.. No!
No, no!
[grunting]
No! No!
[Red John]
'If there's one thing
I can't tolerate'
'it's cheap imitations
of my work.'
[grunting]
Oh.
[panting]
'Do you know who I am?'
Yes.
[dramatic music]
"Tiger, tiger,
burning bright
"in the forests
of the night
"what immortal
hand or eye
"could frame
thy fearful symmetry?"
[panting]
- Aah!
- 'I almost forgot.'
'Kristina would want me
to send her love.'
'She's very fond of you
despite your differences.'
Roll tide.
[panting]
[dramatic music]
[phone ringing]
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You're sure
he said nothing?
Nothing at all?
[sighs]
Nothing.
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
"Tiger, tiger
"burning bright
"in the forests of the night
"what immortal hand or eye
"could frame
thy fearful symmetry?"
[sighs]
[theme music]